Guide to the Robert Fridenberg Collection of Portrait and Topographical Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portraits, Series I
  - L
    - Leu - Lz general, 12 (Box 123, Folder 2140-2151)
    - L. E. L. (Letitia Elizabeth Landon), 1802-1838 (Box 124, Folder 2152)
    - Labé, Louise, 1526?-1566 (Box 124, Folder 2153)
    - La Beaumelle, M. de (Laurent Angliviel), 1726-1773 (Box 124, Folder 2154)
    - Lablache, Luigi, 1794-1858 (Box 124, Folder 2155)
    - La Chaussée, Nivelle de, 1692-1754 (Box 124, Folder 2156)
    - La Condamine, Charles-Marie de, 1701-1774 (Box 124, Folder 2157)
    - Lafarge, Marie, 1816-1852 (Box 124, Folder 2158)
    - Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves Roch Gilbert Du Motier, marquis de, 1757-1834 (Box 124, Folder 2159)
    - La Fayette, Madame de (Marie-Madeleine Pioche de La Vergne), 1634-1693 (Box 124, Folder 2160)
    - La Fontaine, Jean de, 1621-1695 (Box 124, Folder 2161)
    - Lake (Box 124, Folder 2162)
    - Lamartine, Alphonse de, 1790-1869 (Box 124, Folder 2163)
    - Lamb (Box 124, Folder 2164)
    - Lamb, Charles, 1775-1834, 2 (Box 124, Folder 2165-2166)
    - Lamballe, Marie Thérèse Louise de Savoie-Carignan, princesse de (Box 124, Folder 2167)
    - Lambarde, William, 1536-1601 (Box 124, Folder 2168)
    - Lambert (Box 124, Folder 2169)
    - Lambeth (Box 124, Folder 2170)
    - La Motte, M. de (Antoine Houdar), 1672-1731 (Box 124, Folder 2171)
    - Lancaster (Box 124, Folder 2172)
    - Landor, Walter Savage, 1775-1864 (Box 124, Folder 2173)
    - Lang, Andrew, 1844-1912
    - Lansdown/Lansdowne (Box 124, Folder 2174)
    - La Revellière-Lépeaux, Louis-Marie de, 1753-1824 (Box 124, Folder 2175)
    - La Rochefoucauld (Box 124, Folder 2176)
    - La Rochefoucauld, François, duc de, 1613-1680 (Box 124, Folder 2177)
    - La Rochejaquelein, Henri du Vergier, comte de, 1772-1794 (Box 125, Folder 2178)
    - Laruette, Jean Louis, 1731-1792 (Box 125, Folder 2179)
    - Latimer, Hugh, 1485?-1555 (Box 125, Folder 2180)
    - La Tour d'Auvergne (Box 125, Folder 2181)
    - La Trémoille (Box 125, Folder 2182)
    - Laud, William, 1573-1645 (Box 125, Folder 2183)
    - Laugharne, Rowland, d. 1676 (Box 125, Folder 2184)
    - Launey, Bernard René Jourdan, marquis de, 1740-1789 (Box 125, Folder 2185)
    - Laurens (Box 125, Folder 2186)
    - La Vallière, Françoise-Louise de La Baume Le Blanc, duchesse de, 1644-1710 (Box 125, Folder 2187)
    - Law
    - Lawrence (Box 125, Folder 2188)
    - Lawson (Box 125, Folder 2189)
    - Le Brun, Charles, 1619-1690 (Box 125, Folder 2190)
    - Le Chapelier, Isaac-René-Guy, 1754-1794 (Box 125, Folder 2191)
    - Lee (Box 125, Folder 2192)
    - Leeds (Box 125, Folder 2193)
    - Leicester (Box 125, Folder 2194)
    - Leigh (Box 125, Folder 2195)
    - Lekain, Henri Louis Cain, 1728-1778 (Box 125, Folder 2196)
    - Lenclos, Ninon de, 1620-1705 (Box 125, Folder 2197)
    - Lennox/Lenox (Box 125, Folder 2198)
    - Lennox, James Stuart, Duke of, 1612-1655 (Box 125, Folder 2199)
    - Leopold III, Prince of Anhalt-Dessau, 1740-1817 (Box 125, Folder 2200)
    - Leopold Wilhelm, Archduke of Austria, 1614-1662 (Box 125, Folder 2201)
    - Lepeletier de Saint Fargeau, Michel, 1760-1793 (Box 126, Folder 2202)
    - Le Sage, Alain René, 1668-1747 (Box 126, Folder 2203)
    - Lesdiguiéres, François de Bonne, duc de, 1543-1626 (Box 126, Folder 2204)
    - Lesley/Leslie (Box 126, Folder 2205)
    - Lesseps, Ferdinand de, 1805-1894 (Box 126, Folder 2206)
    - L'Estrange, Roger, Sir, 1616-1704 (Box 126, Folder 2207)
    - Leven (Box 126, Folder 2208)
    - Lewis (Box 126, Folder 2209)
    - Lichtenstein (Box 126, Folder 2210)
    - Lichtwer, M. G. (Magnus Gottfried) (Box 126, Folder 2211)
    - Ligne, Charles, prince de, 1757-1792 (Box 126, Folder 2212)
    - Lilburne / Lilbourne (Box 126, Folder 2213)
    - Lincoln (Box 126, Folder 2214)
    - Lindsay/Lindsey (Box 126, Folder 2215)
    - Lingard, John, 1771-1851 (Box 126, Folder 2216)
    - Linguet, Simon Nicolas Henri, 1736-1794 (Box 126, Folder 2217)
    - Linné, Carl von, 1707-1778 (Box 126, Folder 2218)
    - Lionne, Hugues de, 1611-1671 (Box 126, Folder 2219)
    - Lipsius, Justus, 1547-1606 (Box 126, Folder 2220)
    - Lisle (Box 126, Folder 2221)
    - Lithgow, William, 1582-1645? (Box 126, Folder 2222)
    - Littleton / Lettleton / Lyttelton (Box 126, Folder 2223)
    - Livermore (Box 126, Folder 2224)
    - Livingston (Box 126, Folder 2225)
    - Lloyd (Box 127, Folder 2226)
    - Lock, Daniel, 1681-1754 (Box 127, Folder 2227)
    - Locke, John, 1632-1704 (Box 127, Folder 2228)
    - Lockhart (Box 127, Folder 2229)
    - Logan (Box 127, Folder 2230)
    - Londonderry (Box 127, Folder 2231)
    - Longueville, Anne Geneviève de Bourbon-Condé, duchesse de, 1619-1679 (Box 127, Folder 2232)
    - Louise, Princess, daughter of Louis XV, King of France, 1737-1787 (Box 127, Folder 2233)
    - Louvet de Couvray, Jean-Baptiste, 1760-1797 (Box 127, Folder 2234)
    - Louvois, François-Michel Le Tellier, marquis de, 1641-1691 (Box 127, Folder 2235)
    - Lovell, Maria, 1803-1877 (Box 127, Folder 2236)
    - Luckner, Nikolaus, Graf von, 1722-1794 (Box 127, Folder 2237)
    - Luther, Martin, 1483-1546, and Katharina, 1499-1552, 2 (Box 127, Folder 2238-2239)
    - Luxembourg (Box 127, Folder 2240)
    - Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873, and Rosina, 1802-1892 (Box 127, Folder 2241)
    - Lytton, Edward Robert Bulwer Lytton, Earl of, 1831-1891 (Box 127, Folder 2242)
    - Oversize
      - La - Li general, 11 (Box 128 (Oversize), Folder 2243-2253)
      - Lo - Lz general, 5 (Box 129 (Oversize), Folder 2254-2258)
      - L. E. L. - Lawson, 24 (Box 130 (Oversize), Folder 2259-2282)
      - Lee - Livingston, 24 (Box 131 (Oversize), Folder 2283-2306)
      - Lloyd - Lytton, 10 (Box 132 (Oversize), Folder 2307-2316)
  - M
    - McA - Mare general, 13 (Box 133, Folder 2317-2329)
    - Marg - Merk general, 13 (Box 134, Folder 2330-2342)
    - Merl - Montg general, 12 (Box 135, Folder 2343-2354)
    - Month - Mz general, 11 (Box 136, Folder 2355-2365)
    - Macaulay, Thomas Babington Macaulay, Baron, 1800-1859 (Box 137, Folder 2366)
    - McCall, George A. (George Archibald), 1802-1868 (Box 137, Folder 2367)
    - M'Clintock, Francis Leopold, Sir, 1819-1907 (Box 137, Folder 2368)
    - Macdonald, Etienne-Jacques-Joseph-Alexandre, duc de Tarente, 1765-1840 (Box 137, Folder 2369)
    - Mackinnon, Henry, d. 1812 (Box 137, Folder 2370)
    - Mackintosh, James, Sir, 1765-1832 (Box 137, Folder 2371)
    - MacLaurin, Colin, 1698-1746 (Box 137, Folder 2372)
    - Macready, William Charles, 1793-1873 (Box 137, Folder 2373)
    - Machiavelli, Niccolò, 1469-1527 (Box 137, Folder 2374)
    - Madison, James, 1751-1836 (Box 137, Folder 2375)
    - Mailly, Louise Julie, comtesse de, 1710-1751 (Box 137, Folder 2376)
    - Maintenon, Madame de, 1635-1719 (Box 137, Folder 2377)
    - Maitland, John, baron of Thirlestane, 1543-1595 (Box 137, Folder 2378)
    - Malesherbes, Chrétien Guillaume de Lamoignon de, 1721-1794 (Box 137, Folder 2379)
    - Malherbe, François de, 1555-1628 (Box 137, Folder 2380)
    - Malone, Edmond, 1741-1812 (Box 137, Folder 2381)
    - Manchester (Box 137, Folder 2382)
    - Mansfeld, Ernst, graf von, 1585-1626 (Box 137, Folder 2383)
    - Mansfeld, Peter Ernst, Fürst von, 1517-1604 (Box 137, Folder 2384)
    - Mansfield, William Murray, Earl of, 1705-1793 (Box 137, Folder 2385)
    - Manuel, Jacques-Antoine, 1775-1827 (Box 138, Folder 2386)
    - Manuzio, Paolo, 1512-1574 (Box 138, Folder 2387)
    - Marat, Jean Paul, 1743-1793 (Box 138, Folder 2388)
    - Marceau, François-Séverin des Graviers, 1769-1796 (Box 138, Folder 2389)
    - Marigny, Abel François Poisson, marquis de, 1727-1781 (Box 138, Folder 2390)
    - Marillac (Box 138, Folder 2391)
    - Marischal, George Keith, Earl, 1553-1623 (Box 138, Folder 2392)
    - Marivaux, Pierre Carlet de Chamblain de, 1688-1763 (Box 138, Folder 2393)
    - Marlborough, John Churchill, Duke of, 1650-1722 (Box 138, Folder 2394)
    - Marmont, Auguste Frédéric Louis Viesse de, duc de Raguse, 1774-1852 (Box 138, Folder 2395)
    - Marmontel, Jean-François, 1723-1799 (Box 138, Folder 2396)
    - Marnix van St. Aldegonde, Philips van, 1538-1598 (Box 138, Folder 2397)
    - Marot, Clément, 1496-1544 (Box 138, Folder 2398)
    - Marryat, Frederick, 1792-1848 (Box 138, Folder 2399)
    - Mars, Mademoiselle, 1779-1847 (Box 138, Folder 2400)
    - Marshall, John, 1755-1835 (Box 138, Folder 2401)
    - Martin, Henri, 1810-1883 (Box 138, Folder 2402)
    - Marvell, Andrew, 1621-1678 (Box 138, Folder 2403)
    - Masaniello, 1620-1647 (Box 138, Folder 2404)
    - Masséna, André, prince d'Essling, 1758-1817 (Box 138, Folder 2405)
    - Mathews, Charles, 1776-1835 (Box 138, Folder 2406)
    - Maupeou, René-Nicolas-Charles-Augustin de, 1714-1792 (Box 138, Folder 2407)
    - Maurepas, Jean-Frédéric Phélypeaux, comte de, 1701-1781 (Box 138, Folder 2408)
    - Mayenne, Charles de Lorraine, Duc de, 1554-1611 (Box 138, Folder 2409)
    - Mazarin, Hortense Mancini, duchesse de, 1646-1699 (Box 138, Folder 2410)
    - Medici (Box 139, Folder 2411)
    - Medici, Cosimo de', 1389-1464 (Box 139, Folder 2412)
    - Medici, Lorenzo de', 1449-1492 (Box 139, Folder 2413)
    - Melbourne, William Lamb, Viscount, 1779-1848 (Box 139, Folder 2414)
    - Melville (Box 139, Folder 2415)
    - Mendelssohn, Moses, 1729-1786 (Box 139, Folder 2416)
    - Mercier, Louis-Sébastien, 1740-1814 (Box 139, Folder 2417)
    - Metastasio, Pietro, 1698-1782 (Box 139, Folder 2418)
    - Metternich, Clemens Wenzel Lothar, Fürst von, 1773-1859 (Box 139, Folder 2419)
    - Michelet, Jules, 1798-1874 (Box 139, Folder 2420)
    - Middleton, Jane, 1645-1692 (Box 139, Folder 2421)
    - Milton, John, 1608-1674 (Box 139, Folder 2422)
    - Mirabeau, Honoré-Gabriel de Riquetti, comte de, 1749-1791 (Box 139, Folder 2423)
    - Miromesnil, Armand Thomas Hue de, 1723-1796 (Box 139, Folder 2424)
    - Mitchel, O. M. (Ormsby MacKnight), 1809-1862 (Box 139, Folder 2425)
    - Mitford, Mary Russell, 1787-1855 (Box 139, Folder 2426)
    - Molé, Mathieu, 1584-1656 (Box 139, Folder 2427)
    - Molière, 1622-1673 (Box 139, Folder 2428)
    - Molitor, Gabriel-Jean-Joseph, comte de, 1770-1849 (Box 139, Folder 2429)
    - Moncey, Bon-Adrien Jeannot de, duc de Conegliano, 1754-1842 (Box 139, Folder 2430)
    - Monckton, Robert, 1726-1782 (Box 139, Folder 2431)
    - Monluc, Blaise, seigneur de, 1500?-1577 (Box 139, Folder 2432)
    - Monroe, James, 1758-1831 (Box 139, Folder 2433)
    - Montaigne, Michel de, 1533-1592 (Box 140, Folder 2434)
    - Montausier, Charles de Sainte-Maure, duc de, 1610-1690 (Box 140, Folder 2435)
    - Montbazon (Box 140, Folder 2436)
    - Montbazon, Marie de Bretagne d'Avaugour, duchesse de, 1610-1657 (Box 140, Folder 2437)
    - Montcalm de Saint-Véran, Louis-Joseph, marquis de, 1712-1759 (Box 140, Folder 2438)
    - Monteagle of Brandon, Thomas Spring-Rice, Baron, 1790-1866 (Box 140, Folder 2439)
    - Montesquieu, Charles de Secondat, baron de, 1689-1755 (Box 140, Folder 2440)
    - Montesquiou-Fezensac, Anne-Pierre, marquis de, 1739-1798 (Box 140, Folder 2441)
    - Montespan, Françoise-Athénaïs de Rochechouart de Mortemart, marquise de, 1641-1707 (Box 140, Folder 2442)
    - Montmorency (Box 140, Folder 2443)
    - Montmorency, Anne, duc de, 1493-1567 (Box 140, Folder 2444)
    - Montmorency, Henri, duc de, 1595-1632 (Box 140, Folder 2445)
    - Montpensier (Box 140, Folder 2446)
    - Montpensier, Anne-Marie-Louise d'Orléans, duchesse de, 1627-1693 (Box 140, Folder 2447)
    - Moore, John, Sir, 1761-1809 (Box 140, Folder 2448)
    - Moore, Thomas, 1779-1852 (Box 140, Folder 2449)
    - Moray, James Stewart, Earl of, ca. 1531-1570 (Box 140, Folder 2450)
    - More, Thomas, Saint, 1478-1535 (Box 140, Folder 2451)
    - Moreau, Jean Victor Marie, 1763-1813 (Box 140, Folder 2452)
    - Morgan, Daniel, 1736-1802 (Box 141, Folder 2453)
    - Morgan, Lady (Sydney), 1783-1859 (Box 141, Folder 2454)
    - Morris, Gouverneur, 1752-1816 (Box 141, Folder 2455)
    - Morris, Robert, 1734-1806 (Box 141, Folder 2456)
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1791-1872 (Box 141, Folder 2457)
    - Mortier, Édouard Adolphe Casimir Joseph, duc de Trévise, 1768-1835 (Box 141, Folder 2458)
    - Morton, Levi P. (Levi Parsons), 1824-1920 (Box 141, Folder 2459)
    - Moultrie, William, 1730-1805 (Box 141, Folder 2460)
    - Mouton, Georges, comte de Lobau, 1770-1838 (Box 141, Folder 2461)
    - Müller, F. Max (Friedrich Max), 1823-1900 (Box 141, Folder 2462)
    - Munro, Thomas, Sir, 1761-1827 (Box 141, Folder 2463)
    - Munster, George Augustus Frederick FitzClarence, Earl of, 1794-1842 (Box 141, Folder 2464)
    - Murphy, Arthur, 1727-1805 (Box 141, Folder 2465)
    - Murray, George, Sir, 1772-1846 (Box 141, Folder 2466)
    - Murray, John, 1737-1793 (Box 141, Folder 2467)
    - Oversize
      - McA - Man general, 11 (Box 142 (Oversize), Folder 2468-2478)
      - Map - Mez general, 12 (Box 143 (Oversize), Folder 2479-2490)
      - Mi - Mo general, 12 (Box 144 (Oversize), Folder 2491-2502)
      - Mu - Mz general, 3 (Box 145 (Oversize), Folder 2503-2505)
      - Macaulay - Macready, 8 (Box 146 (Oversize), Folder 2506-2513)
      - Machiavelli - Mazarin, 35 (Box 147 (Oversize), Folder 2514-2548)
      - Medici - Montespan, 31 (Box 148 (Oversize), Folder 2549-2579)
      - Montmorency - Murray, 23 (Box 149 (Oversize), Folder 2580-2602)
  - N
    - Na - Nz general, 6 (Box 150, Folder 2603-2608)
    - Napier (Box 151, Folder 2609)
    - Nash/Nashe (Box 151, Folder 2610)
    - Necker, Jacques, 1732-1804, 2 (Box 151, Folder 2611-2612)
    - Necker, Suzanne Curchod, 1739-1794 (Box 151, Folder 2613)
    - Nemours (Box 151, Folder 2614)
    - Newark (Box 151, Folder 2615)
    - Newcastle (Box 151, Folder 2616)
    - Ney, Michel, duc d'Elchingen, 1769-1815 (Box 151, Folder 2617)
    - Nicholas (Box 151, Folder 2618)
    - Noel, Baptist Wriothesley, 1798-1873
    - Norfolk (Box 151, Folder 2619)
    - Norfolk, John Howard, Duke of, 1430?-1485 (Box 151, Folder 2620)
    - Norfolk, Thomas Howard, Duke of, 1443-1524 (Box 151, Folder 2621)
    - Norfolk, Thomas Howard, Duke of, 1473-1554 (Box 151, Folder 2622)
    - Norfolk, Thomas Howard, Duke of, 1538-1572 (Box 151, Folder 2623)
    - Normanby, Constantine Henry Phipps, Marquess of, 1797-1863 (Box 151, Folder 2624)
    - Norris (Box 151, Folder 2625)
    - North (barons, earls, and lords only) (Box 152, Folder 2626)
    - Northampton (Box 152, Folder 2627)
    - Northcote (Box 152, Folder 2628)
    - Northumberland (Box 152, Folder 2629)
    - Northumberland, Algernon Percy, Earl of, 1602-1668 (Box 152, Folder 2630)
    - Nottingham (Box 152, Folder 2631)
    - Nowell, Alexander, 1507?-1602 (Box 152, Folder 2632)
    - Oversize
      - Na - Nz general, 4 (Box 153 (Oversize), Folder 2633-2636)
      - Napier - Nottingham, 15 (Box 153 (Oversize), Folder 2637-2651)
  - O
    - Oa - Oz general, 5 (Box 154, Folder 2652-2656)
    - O'Connell, Daniel, 1775-1847 (Box 154, Folder 2657)
    - Oecolampadius, Johann, 1482-1531 (Box 154, Folder 2658)
    - Old Boots (Box 154, Folder 2659)
    - Oldenbarnevelt (Box 154, Folder 2660)
    - Olivares, Gaspar de Guzmán, conde-duque de, 1587-1645 (Box 154, Folder 2661)
    - Opdam (Box 154, Folder 2662)
    - Opitz (Box 154, Folder 2663)
    - Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 (Box 154, Folder 2664)
    - Orsini (Box 154, Folder 2665)
    - Orsino (Box 154, Folder 2666)
    - Ortelius, Abraham, 1527-1598 (Box 154, Folder 2667)
    - Osten-Sacken, Karl von, 1715-1794
    - Otis, James, 1725-1783 (Box 154, Folder 2668)
    - Oxenstierna (Box 154, Folder 2669)
    - Oversize
      - Oa - Oz general, 3 (Box 155 (Oversize), Folder 2670-2672)
      - O'Connell - Ostensacken, 5 (Box 155 (Oversize), Folder 2673-2677)
  - P
    - Pa - Ph general, 7 (Box 156, Folder 2678-2684)
    - Pi - Pz general, 6 (Box 157, Folder 2685-2690)
    - Paganini, Nicolò, 1782-1840. (Box 158, Folder 2691)
    - Page
    - Paget (Box 158, Folder 2692)
    - Paine (Box 158, Folder 2693)
    - Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809 (Box 158, Folder 2694)
    - Palafox y Melci, José de Rebolledo, duque de Zaragoza, 1776?-1847 (Box 158, Folder 2695)
    - Palmerston, Henry John Temple, Viscount, 1784-1865 (Box 158, Folder 2696)
    - Paoli, Pasquale, 1725-1807 (Box 158, Folder 2697)
    - Pappenheim, Gottfried Heinrich von, 1594-1632 (Box 158, Folder 2698)
    - Parini, Giuseppe, 1729-1799 (Box 158, Folder 2699)
    - Parker
    - Parker, Matthew, 1504-1575 (Box 158, Folder 2700)
    - Parma (Box 158, Folder 2701)
    - Parry, William Edward, Sir, 1790-1855 (Box 158, Folder 2702)
    - Parsons (Box 158, Folder 2703)
    - Paterson (Box 158, Folder 2704)
    - Pauw (Box 158, Folder 2705)
    - Payne
    - Peabody, George, 1795-1869 (Box 158, Folder 2706)
    - Pearson (Box 158, Folder 2707)
    - Peel, Robert, 1788-1850 (Box 158, Folder 2708)
    - Pelissier, Aimable-Jean-Jacques, Duc De Malakoff, 1794-1864 (Box 158, Folder 2709)
    - Pellico, Silvio, 1789-1854 (Box 158, Folder 2710)
    - Pembroke (Box 158, Folder 2711)
    - Pembroke, Anne Clifford Herbert, Countess of, 1590-1676 (Box 158, Folder 2712)
    - Peñaranda de Bracamonte, Gaspar de Bracamonte, conde de, d. 1703 (Box 158, Folder 2713)
    - Penn, William, 1644-1718 (Box 158, Folder 2714)
    - Pennington (Box 158, Folder 2715)
    - Pepys, Samuel, 1633-1703 (Box 158, Folder 2716)
    - Percy (Box 158, Folder 2717)
    - Perignon (Box 159, Folder 2718)
    - Perkins (Box 159, Folder 2719)
    - Perrault, Charles, 1628-1703 (Box 159, Folder 2720)
    - Perry, Oliver Hazard, 1785-1819 (Box 159, Folder 2721)
    - Perry, Matthew Calbraith, 1794-1858
    - Pestalozzi, Johann Heinrich, 1746-1827 (Box 159, Folder 2722)
    - Peterborough (Box 159, Folder 2723)
    - Peters, Hugh, 1598-1660 (Box 159, Folder 2724)
    - Petrarca, Francesco, 1304-1374 (Box 159, Folder 2725)
    - Phillips (Box 159, Folder 2726)
    - Piccolomim (Box 159, Folder 2727)
    - Pichegru, Charles, 1761-1804 (Box 159, Folder 2728)
    - Pinckney, Charles Cotesworth, 1746-1825 (Box 159, Folder 2729)
    - Piombino, Elisa Bonaparte Baciocchi, Principessa di (Box 159, Folder 2730)
    - Piozzi, Hester Lynch, 1741-1821 (Box 159, Folder 2731)
    - Piron, Alexis, 1689-1773 (Box 159, Folder 2732)
    - Pithou (Box 159, Folder 2733)
    - Pitt, William, 1759-1806 (Box 159, Folder 2734)
    - Pitt, William, Earl of Chatham, 1708-1778 (Box 159, Folder 2735)
    - Pizarro, Francisco, ca. 1475-1541 (Box 159, Folder 2736)
    - Platoff, Mattheiu (Box 159, Folder 2737)
    - Poe, Edgar Allan, 1809-1849 (Box 159, Folder 2738)
    - Poitiers, Diane de, Duchess of Valentinois, 1499-1566 (Box 159, Folder 2739)
    - Polignac (Box 159, Folder 2740)
    - Poliziano, Angelo, 1454-1494
    - Pompadour, Jeanne Antoinette Poisson, marquise de, 1721-1764 (Box 159, Folder 2741)
    - Pope (Box 159, Folder 2742)
    - Porson, Richard, 1759-1808 (Box 160, Folder 2743)
    - Porter (Box 160, Folder 2744)
    - Porter, Jane, 1776-1850 (Box 160, Folder 2745)
    - Portland (Box 160, Folder 2746)
    - Potemkin, Grigoriĭ Aleksandrovich, kni︠a︡zʹ, 1739-1791 (Box 160, Folder 2747)
    - Pothier, Robert Joseph, 1699-1772 (Box 160, Folder 2748)
    - Poulett (Box 160, Folder 2749)
    - Prescott, William Hickling, 1796-1859
    - Prevost (Box 160, Folder 2750)
    - Price (Box 160, Folder 2751)
    - Prior, Matthew, 1664-1721 (Box 160, Folder 2752)
    - Prior, Thomas, 1681-1751
    - Prynne, William, 1600-1669 (Box 160, Folder 2753)
    - Pufendorf, Samuel, Freiherr von, 1632-1694 (Box 160, Folder 2754)
    - Puteanus, Erycius, 1574-1646 (Box 160, Folder 2755)
    - Putnam, Israel, 1718-1790 (Box 160, Folder 2756)
    - Puységur, A.-H.-A. de Chastenet (Antoine-Hyacinthe-Anne), comte de, 1752-1807 (Box 160, Folder 2757)
    - Oversize
      - Pa - Pom general, 9 (Box 161 (Oversize), Folder 2758-2766)
      - Pon - Pz general, 4 (Box 162 (Oversize), Folder 2767-2770)
      - Page - Peters, 28 (Box 163 (Oversize), Folder 2771-2798)
      - Petrarca - Putnam, 29 (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2799-2827)
  - Q
    - Qa - Qz general (Box 165 (Oversize), Folder 2828)
    - Quarles (Box 165 (Oversize), Folder 2829)
    - Queensberry (Box 165 (Oversize), Folder 2830)
    - Quevedo (Box 165 (Oversize), Folder 2831)
    - Quinault (Box 165 (Oversize), Folder 2832)
  - R
    - Ra - Re general, 11 (Box 166, Folder 2833-2843)
    - Rh - Ross general, 12 (Box 167, Folder 2844-2855)
    - Rost - Rz general, 7 (Box 168, Folder 2856-2862)
    - Rabaut, Jean-Paul, 1743-1793 (Box 169, Folder 2863)
    - Rabelais, François, ca. 1490-1553? (Box 169, Folder 2864)
    - Racan, Honorat de Bueil, seigneur de, 1589-1670 (Box 169, Folder 2865)
    - Rachel, 1821?-1858 (Box 169, Folder 2866)
    - Racine, Jean, 1639-1699 (Box 169, Folder 2867)
    - Racine, Louis, 1692-1763 (Box 169, Folder 2868)
    - Raleigh, Walter, Sir, 1552?-1618 (Box 169, Folder 2869)
    - Ramsay, Allan, 1686-1758 (Box 169, Folder 2870)
    - Randolph, John, 1773-1833 (Box 169, Folder 2871)
    - Raynal, abbé (Guillaume-Thomas-François), 1713-1796 (Box 169, Folder 2872)
    - Read, George, 1733-1798 (Box 169, Folder 2873)
    - Récamier, Jeanne Françoise Julie Adélaïde Bernard, 1777-1849 (Box 169, Folder 2874)
    - Reed, Isaac, 1742-1807 (Box 169, Folder 2875)
    - Reed, Joseph, 1741-1785 (Box 169, Folder 2876)
    - Reede-Ginckel, Godard, Baron van, 1644-1703 (Box 169, Folder 2877)
    - Regnard, Jean François, 1655-1709 (Box 169, Folder 2878)
    - Renan, Ernest, 1823-1892 (Box 169, Folder 2879)
    - Renaud, Cecile, 1774-1794 (Box 169, Folder 2880)
    - Rennie, John, 1761-1821 (Box 169, Folder 2881)
    - Retz (Box 169, Folder 2882)
    - Reubell, Jean-François, 1747-1807 (Box 169, Folder 2883)
    - Reynolds, Joshua, Sir, 1723-1792 (Box 169, Folder 2884)
    - Richardson, Samuel, 1689-1761 (Box 169, Folder 2885)
    - Richelieu, Armand Jean du Plessis, duc de, 1585-1642 (Box 169, Folder 2886)
    - Richelieu, Louis François Armand du Plessis, duc de, 1696-1788 (Box 169, Folder 2887)
    - Richmond (Box 170, Folder 2888)
    - Richmond, Frances Howard, Duchess of, 1578-1639 (Box 170, Folder 2889)
    - Richmond, Ludovic Stuart, Duke of, 1574-1624 (Box 170, Folder 2890)
    - Richmond and Lennox, Charles Lennox, Duke of, 1735-1806 (Box 170, Folder 2891)
    - Richmond and Lennox, Frances Teresa Stuart, Duchess of, 1648-1702 (Box 170, Folder 2892)
    - Ridley, Nicholas, 1500?-1555 (Box 170, Folder 2893)
    - Rivarol, Antoine, 1753-1801 (Box 170, Folder 2894)
    - Rivington, James, 1724-1802 (Box 170, Folder 2895)
    - Robertson, William, 1721-1793 (Box 170, Folder 2896)
    - Robespierre, Maximilien, 1758-1794 (Box 170, Folder 2897)
    - Rochester (Box 170, Folder 2898)
    - Rockingham, Charles Watson-Wentworth, Marquis of, 1730-1782 (Box 170, Folder 2899)
    - Rodney, George Brydges Rodney, Baron, 1719-1792 (Box 170, Folder 2900)
    - Roebuck, John Arthur, 1802-1879 (Box 170, Folder 2901)
    - Rogers, Samuel, 1763-1855 (Box 170, Folder 2902)
    - Rohan (Box 170, Folder 2903)
    - Roland de La Platière, Jean-Marie, 1734-1793 (Box 170, Folder 2904)
    - Roland de La Platière, Marie-Jeanne, 1754-1793 (Box 170, Folder 2905)
    - Rollin, Charles, 1661-1741 (Box 170, Folder 2906)
    - Ronsard, Pierre de, 1524-1585 (Box 170, Folder 2907)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 (Box 171, Folder 2908)
    - Roscoe, William, 1753-1831 (Box 171, Folder 2909)
    - Rousseau, Jean-Baptiste, 1670-1741 (Box 171, Folder 2910)
    - Rousseau, Jean-Jacques, 1712-1778 (Box 171, Folder 2911)
    - Rowe, Nicholas, 1674-1718 (Box 171, Folder 2912)
    - Rupert, Prince, Count Palatine, 1619-1682 (Box 171, Folder 2913)
    - Russell, John Russell, Earl, 1792-1878 (Box 171, Folder 2914)